Guide to the Willard Dickerman Straight papers, 1825-1925.
Straight, Willard Dickerman papers, 1825-1925.
- Visual Materials
  - Associates (autographed, annotated)
    - Elliot & Fry, London, England 1904-1911 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Associates (autographed, annotated)
    - Hart, Robert 1904-1911 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Associates (autographed, annotated)
    - Jordan, John N. 1904-1911 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Associates (autographed, annotated)
    - MacDonald, Claude 1904-1911 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Associates (autographed, annotated)
    - MacDonald, Ethel 1904-1911 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Associates (autographed, annotated)
    - Marvin, George D. 1904-1911 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Associates (autographed, annotated)
    - Morrison, George E. 1904-1911 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Associates (autographed, annotated)
    - Portraits 1904-1911 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Chinese Family Portraits (annotated, autographed)
    - Fu Hsing, Photographer, Tientsin 1908c. (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Wedding and Honeymoon
    - Architecture, Exterior 1911 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Wedding and Honeymoon
    - Bishop, Beatrice 1911 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Wedding and Honeymoon
    - Fred Boissonnas, Geneva, Switzerland 1911 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Wedding and Honeymoon
    - Italy, Stresa 1911 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Wedding and Honeymoon
    - Landscapes 1911 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Wedding and Honeymoon
    - Paget, Dorothy W. 1911 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Wedding and Honeymoon
    - Paget, Olive C. 1911 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Wedding and Honeymoon
    - Portraits 1911 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Wedding and Honeymoon
    - Straight, Dorothy W. 1911 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Wedding and Honeymoon
    - Straight, Willard D. 1911 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Family Portraits, Children
    - Bend, Beatrice 1913-1918 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Family Portraits, Children
    - Casenave, Maurice 1913-1918 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Family Portraits, Children
    - Elizabeth Dickson, New York, New York 1913-1918 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Family Portraits, Children
    - Fletcher, Henry P. 1913-1918 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Family Portraits, Children
    - Helen McCaul 1913-1918 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Family Portraits, Children
    - Stephens, Henry M. 1913-1918 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Family Portraits, Children
    - Straight, Dorothy W. 1913-1918 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Family Portraits, Children
    - Straight, Michael W. 1913-1918 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Family Portraits, Children
    - Straight, Whitney W. 1913-1918 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Family Portraits, Children
    - Straight, Willard D. 1913-1918 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Family Portraits, Children
    - Portraits 1913-918 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Straight Children
    - Paul Thompson, New York, New York 1921 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Straight Children
    - Children 1921c (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Straight Children
    - Straight Beatrice W. 1921c. (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Straight Children
    - Straight, Michael W. 1921c. (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Straight Children
    - Straight, Whitney W. 1921c. (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Westbury (annotated)
    - Apple Green, Westbury, New York n.d. (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Westbury (annotated)
    - New York, Westbury n.d. (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - India House
    - Architecture, Interior n.d. (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - India House
    - India House n.d. (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Paintings of Clipper Ships
    - B. Tindall n.d. (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Paintings of Clipper Ships
    - India House n.d. (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Paintings of Clipper Ships
    - Lai Fong n.d. (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Paintings of Clipper Ships
    - Paintings n.d. (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Paintings of Clipper Ships
    - Ships n.d. (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Chinese Imperial Maritime Customs Service
    - China, Nanking 1902 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Chinese Imperial Maritime Customs Service
    - Chinese Imperial Maritime Customs Service College 1902 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Chinese Imperial Maritime Customs Service
    - People, Identified Groups of Westerners 1902 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Chinese Imperial Maritime Customs Service
    - Straight, Willard D. 1902 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Chinese Imperial Maritime Customs Service
    - Yoong Kwong, Photographer 1902 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - U.S. Legation, Peking (annotated)
    - Gillett, Frederick 1905c. (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Legation, Seoul (annotated, autographed)
    - Paddock, Gordon 1905 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Legation, Seoul (annotated, autographed)
    - People, Unidentified Groups of Westerners 1905 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Legation, Seoul (annotated, autographed)
    - Portraits 1905 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Legation, Seoul (annotated, autographed)
    - Roosevelt, Alice L. 1905 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Legation, Seoul (annotated, autographed)
    - Boardman, Mabel L. 1905 c. (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Legation, Seoul (annotated, autographed)
    - K. Murakami, Seoui, Korea 1905c. (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Legation, Seoul (annotated, autographed)
    - Korea, Seoul 1905c. (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Legation, Seoul (annotated, autographed)
    - Longworth, Nicholas 1905c. (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Legation, Seoul (annotated, autographed)
    - Macarthur, Douglas 1905c. (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Legation, Seoul (annotated, autographed)
    - Morgan, Edwin V. 1905c. (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Legation, Seoul (annotated, autographed)
    - Social Life 1905c. (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Legation, Seoul (annotated, autographed)
    - Straight, Willard D. 1905c. (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Legation, Seoul (annotated, autographed)
    - U.S. Legation, Seoul 1905c. (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Havana (annotated)
    - Architecture, Exterior 1906 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Havana (annotated)
    - Architecture, Interior 1906 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Havana (annotated)
    - Cuba, Havana 1906 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Havana (annotated)
    - Longworth, Alice R. 1906 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Havana (annotated)
    - Longworth, Nicholas 1906 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Havana (annotated)
    - Morgan, Edwin V. 1906 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Havana (annotated)
    - Straight, Willard D. 1906 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Havana (annotated)
    - U.S. Legation, Havan 1906 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Consul General, Mukden (annotated)
    - People, Groups of Chinese 1907 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Consul General, Mukden (annotated)
    - People, Groups of Westerners 1907 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Consul General, Mukden (annotated)
    - Portraits 1907 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Consul General, Mukden (annotated)
    - Rockhill, William w. 1907 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Consul General, Mukden (annotated)
    - Arnell, Charles J. 1907 c. (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Consul General, Mukden (annotated)
    - Fulford, Harry E. 1907c. (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Consul General, Mukden (annotated)
    - Hagiwara, S. 1907c. (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Consul General, Mukden (annotated)
    - Marvin, George D. 1907c. (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Consul General, Mukden (annotated)
    - Mezger, Otto 1907c. (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Consul General, Mukden (annotated)
    - Morrison, George E. 1907c. (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Consul General, Mukden (annotated)
    - Straight, Willard D. 1907c. (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Consul General, Mukden (annotated)
    - T'Ang, Shao-Yi 1907c. (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Consul General, Mukden (annotated)
    - U.S. Consulate, Mukden 1907c. (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Consul General, Mukden (autographed)
    - China, Manchuria, Mukden 1907c. (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Consul General, Mukden (annotated)
    - People, Groups of Chinese 1907 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Consul General, Mukden (annotated)
    - People, Groups of Westerners 1907 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Consul General, Mukden (annotated)
    - Portraits 1907 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Consul General, Mukden (autographed)
    - Architecture, Exterior 1907 c. (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Consul General, Mukden (autographed)
    - Arnell, Charles J. 1907 c. (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Consul General, Mukden (autographed)
    - China, Manchuria, Mukden 1907c. (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Consul General, Mukden (autographed)
    - Fulford, Harry E. 1907c. (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Consul General, Mukden (autographed)
    - Marvin, George D. 1907c. (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Consul General, Mukden (autographed)
    - Mezger, Otto 1907c. (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Consul General, Mukden (autographed)
    - Straight, Willard D. 1907c. (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Consul General, Mukden (autographed)
    - U.S. Consulate, Mukden 1907c. (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Chinese Family Portraits (annotated, autographed)
    - People, Groups of Chinese 1908 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Chinese Family Portraits (annotated, autographed)
    - Portraits 1908 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Chinese Family Portraits (annotated, autographed)
    - P'U-Lun, Princess 1908 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Chinese Family Portraits (annotated, autographed)
    - China, Tientsin 1908c. (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Chinese Family Portraits (annotated, autographed)
    - Sze, Sao-Ke Alfred 1908c. (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Chinese Family Portraits (annotated, autographed)
    - T'Ang, Shao-Yi 1908c. (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Chinese Associates (annotated)
    - Portraits 1910 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Chinese Associates (annotated)
    - A-MU-ERH-Ling-Kuei 1910 c. (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Chinese Associates (annotated)
    - Chao, Erh-Hsun 1910c. (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Chinese Associates (annotated)
    - China, Manchuria 1910c. (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Chinese Associates (annotated)
    - China, Peking 1910c. (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Chinese Associates (annotated)
    - Dress 1910c. (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Chinese Associates (annotated)
    - S. Yamamoto, Peking 1910c. (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Chinese Associates (annotated)
    - Tao, Tien-Chun 1910c. (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Chinese Associates (annotated)
    - To-Wen 1910c. (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Chinese Associates (annotated)
    - Tsai Hsun 1910c. (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Gift Enlargements (autographed)
    - China, Manchuria 1908 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Gift Enlargements (autographed)
    - Straight, Willard D. 1908 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Gift Enlargements (autographed)
    - Tombs 1908 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Temples
    - Architecture, Exterior n.d. (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Temples
    - Sculpture n.d. (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Temples
    - Temples n.d. (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Mounted Chinese Scenes
    - Landscapes n.d. (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Mounted Chinese Scenes
    - People, Unidentified Groups of Chinese n.d. (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Mounted Chinese Scenes
    - Temples n.d. (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Mountain Scenes (commercial photographs)
    - Canada n.d. (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Mountain Scenes (commercial photographs)
    - Switzerland n.d. (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Views of India (commercial photographs)
    - India n.d. (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Russo-Japanese War
    - Russo-Japanese War 1905c. (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Voyage to China
    - Transportation, Jinrikshas 1901 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Voyage to China (annotated)
    - Ceylon 1901 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Russo-Japanese War
    - Korean Army 1905c. (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Alice Roosevelt Longworth
    - Cuba 1905-1906 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Alice Roosevelt Longworth
    - Korea 1905-1906 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Alice Roosevelt Longworth
    - Longworth, Alice R. 1905-1906 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Alice Roosevelt Longworth
    - Parades 1905-1906 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Alice Roosevelt Longworth
    - People, Unidentified Groups 1905-1906 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Alice Roosevelt Longworth
    - People, Unidentified Individuals 1905-1906 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Alice Roosevelt Longworth
    - Transportation, Sedan Chairs 1905-1906 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Mukden
    - China, Manchuria, Mukden 1906c (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Mukden (annotated)
    - People, Unidentified Groups 1906 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Mukden (annotated)
    - People, Unidentified Individuals 1906 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Great Wall
    - China n.d. (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Great Wall
    - Great Wall n.d. (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Westerners in China
    - China 1909 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Westerners in China (annotated)
    - People, Unidentified Westerners 1909 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Westerners in China (annotated)
    - Sculpture 1909 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Chinese Buildings
    - Architecture, Exterior n.d. (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Chinese Buildings
    - Bridges n.d. (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Chinese Buildings
    - China n.d. (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Chinese Buildings
    - Temples n.d. (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Chinese Street Scenes
    - Ceremonies n.d. (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Chinese Street Scenes
    - China n.d. (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Chinese Street Scenes
    - Street Scenes n.d. (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Chinese Street Scenes
    - Porters 1905 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Chinese Street Scenes
    - Korea 1905c. (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Chinese Street Scenes
    - Occupations 1905c. (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Chinese Street Scenes
    - Street Scenes 1905c. (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Chinese Street Scenes
    - Women 1905c. (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Chinese Street Scenes
    - China 1905c. (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Chinese Street Scenes
    - Dress 1905c. (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Chinese Street Scenes
    - Korea 1905c. (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Chinese Street Scenes
    - Street Scenes 1905c. (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Railroads
    - China 1902-1910 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Railroads
    - Korea 1902-1910 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Railroads
    - People, Unidentified Groups 1902-1910 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Railroads
    - People, Unidentified Individuals 1902-1910 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Railroads
    - Railroads 1902-1910 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Railroads
    - Railroads, Handcars 1902-1910 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Railroads
    - Railroads, Narrow-Gauge 1902-1910 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Railroads
    - Railroads, Stations 1902-1910 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Railroads
    - Transportation, Railroads 1902-1910 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Railroads
    - Trans-Siberian Railroad 1902-1910 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Railroads
    - China, Manchuria 1902-1910 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Railroads
    - Korea 1902-1910 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Railroads
    - People, Unidentified Groups 1902-1910 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Railroads
    - Railroads 1902-1910 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Railroads
    - Railroads, Handcars 1902-1910 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Railroads
    - Railroads, Stations 1902-1910 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Railroads
    - Transportation, Railroads 1902-1910 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Rural Scenes
    - Lumber Yard n.d. (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Rural Scenes
    - Transporation, Oxcarts n.d. (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Rural Scenes
    - Village Scenes n.d. (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Maritime Scenes
    - Boats n.d. (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Maritime Scenes
    - China, Hankow n.d. (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Maritime Scenes
    - China, Hanyang n.d. (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Maritime Scenes
    - Maritime Scenes n.d. (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Maritime Scenes
    - Transportation, Junks n.d. (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Maritime Scenes
    - Boats n.d. (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Maritime Scenes
    - Docks n.d. (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Maritime Scenes
    - Harbors n.d. (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Maritime Scenes
    - Ships n.d. (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Maritime Scenes
    - Transporation, Sailboats n.d. (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Maritime Scenes
    - Transportation, Steamships n.d. (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Chinese People
    - People, Unidentified Groups 1911 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Chinese People
    - People, Unidentified Individual Chinese 1911 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Chinese People
    - Children 1911c. (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Chinese People
    - China 1911c. (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Chinese People
    - Dress 1911c. (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Chinese People
    - Straight, Dorothy W. 1911c. (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Chinese People
    - Women 1911c. (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Views of China
    - Architecture, Exterior n.d. (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Views of China
    - Docks n.d. (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Views of China
    - Street Scenes n.d. (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Scenes
    - China n.d. (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Scenes
    - Landscapes n.d. (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Scenes
    - People, Unidentified Individuals n.d. (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Scenes
    - Philippines n.d. (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Western Men
    - People, Groups of Westerners 1911 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Western Men
    - People, Individual Westerners 1911 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Western Men
    - Casenave, Maurice 1911c. (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Western Men
    - China 1911c. (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Western Men
    - French, Charles 1911c. (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Western Men
    - Straight, Willard D. 1911c. (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Western People
    - People, Groups of Westerners 1911 (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Western People
    - People, Individual Westerners 1911 (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Western People
    - Residence, Peking 1911 (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Western People
    - China, Peking 1911c. (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Western People
    - Straight, Dorothy W. 1911c. (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Western People
    - Straight, Willard D. 1911c. (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Western People
    - Women 1911c. (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Groups of Westerners
    - People, Groups 1911 (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Groups of Westerners
    - Calhoun, William J. 1911c. (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Groups of Westerners
    - Casenave, Maurice 1911c. (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Groups of Westerners
    - China 1911c. (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Groups of Westerners
    - Straight, Dorothy W. 1911c. (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Groups of Westerners
    - Straight, Willard D. 1911c. (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - People in China
    - People, Individual Westerners 1911 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - People in China
    - People, Unidentified Individual Chinese 1911 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - People in China
    - China 1911c. (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - People in China
    - Straight, Dorothy W. 1911c. (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - People in China
    - Straight, Willard D. 1911c. (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - Manila
    - Architecture, Exterior 1912 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - Manila
    - Landscapes 1912 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - Manila
    - Palaces 1912 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - Manila
    - People, Unidentified Groups 1912 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - Manila
    - Philippines, Manila 1912 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - Manila (annotated)
    - Dress 1912 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - English Country Houses
    - Architecture, Exterior 1912 c. (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - English Country Houses
    - Gardens 1912c. (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - English Country Houses
    - Straight, Dorothy W. 1912c. (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - English Country Parties
    - England 1912c. (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - Mrs. Bend and the Children
    - Bend, Marraine 1915 c. (Box 71, Folder 25)
  - Mrs. Bend and the Children
    - Straight Beatrice W. 1915c. (Box 71, Folder 25)
  - Mrs. Bend and the Children
    - Straight, Whitney W. 1915c. (Box 71, Folder 25)
  - Straight Family
    - Portraits 1917 (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Straight Family
    - New York, Westbury 1917c. (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Straight Family
    - Straight Beatrice W. 1917c. (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Straight Family
    - Straight, Dorothy W. 1917c. (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Straight Family
    - Straight, Michael W. 1917c. (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Straight Family
    - Straight, Whitney W. 1917c. (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Straight Family
    - Straight, Willard D. 1917c. (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Plattsburg
    - Camp of Intruction, Regular Troops, Plattsburg, New York 1915 (Box 71, Folder 27)
  - Plattsburg
    - New York, Plattsburg 1915 (Box 71, Folder 27)
  - Voyage on the Transport "Logan"
    - People, Unidentified Individual Westerners 1917 (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - Voyage on the Transport "Logan"
    - American Expeditionary Forces 1917 c. (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - Voyage on the Transport "Logan"
    - Ships 1917c. (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - Westbury
    - Architecture, Exterior 1926 c. (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - Westbury
    - Gardens 1926c. (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - Westbury
    - New York, Westbury 1926c. (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - Views of Mexico (commercial photographs)
    - C.B. Waite, Mexico City n.d. (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Views of Mexico (commercial photographs)
    - Mexico n.d. (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Views of Mexico (commercial photographs)
    - C.B. Waite, Mexico City n.d. (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Views of Mexico (commercial photographs)
    - Mexico n.d. (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Views of Mexico (commercial photographs)
    - C.B. Waite, Mexico City n.d. (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Views of Mexico (commercial photographs)
    - Mexico n.d. (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Views of Mexico (commercial photographs)
    - C.B. Waite, Mexico City n.d. (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Views of Mexico (commercial photographs)
    - Mexico n.d. (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Nichols House, Samuel McIntire architect, 1782 (commercial photographs
    - Architectural Detail n.d. (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Nichols House, Samuel McIntire architect, 1782 (commercial photographs
    - Architecture, Exterior n.d. (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Nichols House, Samuel McIntire architect, 1782 (commercial photographs
    - Architecture, Interior n.d. (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Nichols House, Samuel McIntire architect, 1782 (commercial photographs
    - Frank Cousins Art Co., Salem, Massachusettes n.d. (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Nichols House, Samuel McIntire architect, 1782 (commercial photographs
    - Gardens n.d. (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Nichols House, Samuel McIntire architect, 1782 (commercial photographs)
    - Massachusetts, Salem n.d. (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Massachusetts Architecture (commercial photographs)
    - Architectural Detail n.d. (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Massachusetts Architecture (commercial photographs)
    - Architecture, Exterior n.d. (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Massachusetts Architecture (commercial photographs)
    - Architecture, Interior n.d. (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Massachusetts Architecture (commercial photographs)
    - Fireplaces n.d. (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Massachusetts Architecture (commercial photographs)
    - Frank Cousins Art Co., Salem, Massachusettes n.d. (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Massachusetts Architecture (commercial photographs)
    - Massachusetts, Salem n.d. (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - French Architecture (commercial photographs
    - Architecture, Exterior n.d. (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - French Architecture (commercial photographs
    - France n.d. (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - German and English Architecture (commercial photographs)
    - Architecture, Exterior n.d. (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - German and English Architecture (commercial photographs)
    - England n.d. (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Italian Architecture (commercial photographs
    - Architecture, Exterior n.d. (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Italian Architecture (commercial photographs
    - Italy n.d. (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Photographs of Artwork (commercial photographs)
    - Italy n.d. (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Photographs of Artwork (commercial photographs)
    - Paintings n.d. (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Photographs of Artwork (commercial photographs)
    - Sculpture n.d. (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Scenes of China and Korea (commercial photographs)
    - China n.d. (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Scenes of China and Korea (commercial photographs)
    - Korea n.d. (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Scenes of India (commercial photographs
    - India n.d. (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Java- Buitenzorg Botanical Gardens (commercial photographs)
    - Java, Buitenzorg n.d. (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Java-Buitenzorg Botanical Gardens (commercial photographs)
    - Botanical Gardens, Buitenzorg, Java n.d. (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Java People (commercial photographs)
    - Dress n.d. (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Java People (commercial photographs)
    - Java n.d. (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Java Scenes (commercial photographs)
    - Java n.d. (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Java People (commercial photographs)
    - Dress n.d. (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Java People (commercial photographs)